[Boyd] Previously on From...
- [screaming]
- What's wrong with her?!
- What happened to you?
- What do you mean?
Since you fell asleep and
your eyes got all white,
you've been different.
Do you feel that?
We should go.
You feel it.
You do.
What the hell's going on?
It was my idea. She
needed to come out here.
Mom saw this place
when she was little.
There might be a part of
you that wants so badly
for all of this to make sense.
This wasn't just a
random nightmare, Jim.
This was a dream
I had for months.
Miranda said she was chosen.
If you were destined
to come to this place,
then one way or another,
you were always gonna come
to that tree in the road.
He knows things.
I heard him tell Christopher
a story about this place once.
We'll make him tell it again.
Can I go in your basement?
I need him to tell me a secret.
Help me, Elgin.
I can save all of you.
[camera shutter clicking]
[ominous music playing]
Is this really where it happens?
Whatever is inside me,
it's getting stronger.
The cravings... they're
getting stronger.
- I'm angry all the time.
- It's okay.
- Aah!
- Fatima, it's gonna be okay.
- I said go!
- [gasps]
Help!
What have I done?
What have I done?!
[crow cawing]
Come on.
Have a seat.
Have a seat. Tell
me what happened.
We were in the...
the greenhouse.
I was...
And... and I didn't wanna eat
those rotting things anymore.
[cries] Tillie came in,
and she was trying to help me,
and I felt this wave of...
of anger come over me,
like this rage.
It was like this thing...
inside me. It was...
It was like I was
there, but I wasn't.
And... and I felt my hand
reach for the shears.
And I couldn't stop.
[breathing shakily]
I didn't wanna do it.
- There was nothing I could do.
- Here's what we're gonna do.
You're gonna stay
out here tonight.
And come morning,
Ellis and I are gonna
figure out the best way...
We're gonna figure out
how we move forward.
There's no way forward.
Hey. Look at me.
You are my family.
And what happened back there,
we are gonna find a
way to deal with it.
Okay?
Fatima.
Okay.
If you need to eat...
No, no, no, no. Please...
Please take that away.
Look, whatever is
happening to you...
Take it away!
I don't want it
to get any worse.
So, you need to eat, you eat.
What about Tillie?
We just... I left her there.
- I left her there.
- [Boyd] Okay.
- My God, I left her there.
- Listen to me, listen.
We're gonna have to
let someone find her.
Oh, my God. [crying]
No. No, no, no. I know.
Hey. Look at me, look at me.
Look, I need you to be
strong right now, okay?
I need you to be... Ellis
needs you to be strong.
Please.
[breathing shakily]
That's right.
Okay.
Now it's getting dark.
This door stays
closed, no matter what.
Right.
We're gonna be okay.
[sobs]
["Que Sera, Sera (Whatever
Will Be, Will Be)" playing]
♪ When I was just a little boy ♪
♪ I asked my father ♪
♪ "What will I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I be handsome?" ♪
♪ "Will I be rich?" ♪
♪ Here's what he said to me ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ Whatever will be will be ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ What will be will be ♪
♪ Now I have
children of my own ♪
♪ They ask their father ♪
♪ "What will I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I be pretty?" ♪
♪ "Will I be rich?" ♪
♪ I tell them tenderly ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ Whatever will be will be ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ What will be will be ♪
[man in distance] We're
coming in two minutes!
Hey, uh... [clears throat]
I'll, uh, I'll catch
up with you guys later.
Hey, Ethan, Ethan...
[footsteps ascend stairs]
[sighs]
[bottle clatters]
[clatter in distance]
[clatter continues]
Hello?
[grunt]
Okay.
Hello?!
Hey. Uh, sorry. [chuckles]
Who the fuck are you?
Sorry, I'm, um...
Henry Kavanaugh.
You probably know my son.
Victor?
Oh.
Right.
Nice to meet you.
Same.
Uh... it's quite the
set-up you've got.
You making any progress?
No, not really.
I hope you don't mind if I
grab a little pick-me-up.
Help yourself.
Cheers.
[sighs]
[coughing]
[humming]
[door opens]
We need help!
Help! I need help!
- Somebody get Donna!
- What is it?
[man] It's Tillie!
Shit.
[camera shutter clicks]
[ominous music playing]
I'm going home.
Have you seen
Kristi or Marielle?
- Uh, no.
- Can you just tell them
I said thank you for
letting me stay the night?
I don't get a thank you?
Thank you, Randall, for
letting me stay at the place
that Marielle and Kristi
are letting you stay at.
You're welcome.
We should go back.
To that place, whatever
it is, we should...
we should go back
and check it out.
What?
Well, typically, when
a place makes the hair
on the back of my neck stand up,
it's enough for me to stay away.
Yeah, but we both felt it.
Right? What if it can, like,
I don't know, help with
whatever's happening...
And what if it
makes it worse? Huh?
Look...
There is nothing here
that wants to help us.
Okay? Nothing.
So, stay the fuck
away from that place.
Right?
Remember what I
said. Anybody asks,
you and Fatima were with
me last night. Okay?
What if we just
tell them the truth
and explain what happened?
- Ellis...
- That it wasn't her fault.
I know. I know.
Maybe some of those people
will understand that.
There's no version of
us explaining this away.
Look, they're gonna
put her in the Box.
I'm not gonna let that
happen. Look at me.
happen. Get yourself together.
Go in there, get
up to your room,
put some things in a
bag. Don't pack too much,
just enough for her
to spend a couple days
out there at the shack.
And what are you gonna do?
I'm gonna... [clears throat]
- [Kenny] Boyd!
- Buy us some time. Hey!
[Kenny] Hey, uh...
We found something.
Anyone see anything?
Uh, not that we've...
Not that we've heard so far.
Any idea when this happened?
Could've been this morning.
It could've been last night.
There's not a whole lot
of people coming in,
with the snow and everything.
[Acosta] Those things
that come out at night,
I'm guessing they don't
use gardening shears?
No.
We should talk to
everyone in the house.
[Kenny] Boyd?
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Start talking to people.
I'll take Ellis out
to walk the road.
- Walk the road?
- This could've been done
by people we know
or people we don't.
We need to rule
out the possibility
we had any new
arrivals yesterday
that we don't know about.
- [Boyd] All right?
- Yeah.
Yeah. Hey.
I know, you're not
my deputy, but...
Yeah, no, I got it.
We'll get the
interviews started.
Yeah.
Hey, Sheriff?
We good?
Let's find out who did this.
[gasps]
Hey, you okay?
Hell, we're gonna
have to talk to Sara.
- It wasn't her.
- [Donna] You don't know that.
And I am not the only person
who's gonna be asking about her.
[breathing shakily]
If you don't think
she did it, fine.
Then, we'll just have to...
go talk to her and make sure.
- Listen...
- No, no, no, you listen.
Hiding every night from those
things, that's one thing.
But this? This is something
that people are gonna
have to blame someone for.
And if we don't figure out who,
then it's gonna be Sara,
whether she did it or not.
Okay.
You get things
straightened out here,
then meet me at the station, and
we will talk to her together.
[Sara] "Hello, Victor.
Do you want to play today?
I can tell you a secret."
No, no, not... not like
that! I just... I told you!
It doesn't sound
like that, Sara!
I'm doing the best that I can!
I'm trying everything
that I know!
I don't know what
you want, Victor!
- [mumbling]
- [thudding]
- Hey, hey, hey!
- [Victor] No!
No! He d... he
doesn't... you need...
he needs to talk, and
you're not doing it right!
I'm doing the best that I can!
No, you're not doing
it good enough!
No, you're not good enough.
You're not good enough!
- Victor! Hey!
- You're not good enough!
- Hey, don't! Stop! Stop!
- Stop! Stop!
Look, I know you want all
this to mean something,
and this place has you
convinced that you need
to save these children.
It's got you trying to fix
something that we can never...
[sighs]
Do you know why the
phone is off the wall?
Because it rang the other day,
and the voice on the other
end said his name was Thomas.
What?
Something here knows
things about us,
and it knows which
buttons to push.
[knock on door]
[exhales]
[knocking continues]
I'm sorry.
I know I shouldn't
be here, but...
Victor is in my basement,
and he's in really bad shape.
He said he only
wants to talk to you.
I wouldn't have come
if it wasn't important.
Just wait there.
I'll get my coat.
I have to go.
[Elgin] Hello?
[door closes]
- Hey.
- [Elgin gasps]
If you're looking for drugs,
you're in the wrong spot.
Oh, no, no.
Uh, no, I was... just
looking for a Band-Aid.
- Oh.
- I cut my foot.
Mm. You better not
let Kristi or Marielle
find you rooting
through their shit.
You hear about Tillie?
Yeah.
It's fucked up.
Hey. I'm sorry I
was so hard on you
on the bus that day.
I guess you were right.
We should've turned around.
Sorry I, uh, threw up
all over your shirt.
[chuckles] Yeah.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[Sara] Victor?
Oh.
Oh. Oh, you're here.
- [Tabitha] Hi, Victor. Hi.
- Good. Come.
Hey.
[grunts] You sit...
come sit here.
- Okay.
- There. Take this.
Okay.
- Okay.
- Victor, what are we...
You were there. You were there
when I remembered Eloise,
so you're the one that
can make him talk.
Okay, Victor, I'm so sorry.
I don't know... I
don't understand.
He needs to tell me! You
need to make him tell me.
[Tabitha] Tell you what, Victor?
[Victor] The secrets
that he told Christopher
'cause he can help us.
[Tabitha] I'm sorry, honey.
He's... he's just a doll.
[Victor] No! No, you
have to be the one!
You have to be the one!
- Okay, okay!
- You have to be the one!
- [Tabitha] Victor! Hey! Hey!
- Hey! Victor, stop it!
- Stop it! Don't do that!
- You have to be the one.
Calm down. Don't do
that, Victor, please.
Shh. Look at me. Look
at me. Look at me.
Look at me, Victor.
It's okay. You're okay.
- [Tabitha] You're okay.
- Okay.
- It's okay.
- Yeah.
Do you want to draw a picture?
No. No, it doesn't
work like that.
See, the pictures
always remembered
so that I didn't have to.
But I never drew one,
so now it's gone, and I can't...
I can't remember.
No. No, okay, okay.
First of all, sit down.
It's okay. You're okay.
You're okay. Sit down, okay?
It's okay, Victor.
Just sit down.
Nothing is gone.
Nothing's gone.
It's okay. Um...
Tell me about... tell
me about the doll.
His name is Jasper.
Jasper? Okay. Uh,
tell me about Jasper.
I heard him once,
telling Christopher things
that we need to know.
But I don't remember.
[Tabitha] Hey, it's
okay. Victor, look at me.
- But...
- Look at me.
We'll remember together,
just like last time.
- Okay.
- We can do this together, okay?
Yeah. [sniffs]
Hello?
Anyone home?
Hey.
Uh... how were things
at the settlement?
Uh, not great.
Oh.
Listen, your brother's upstairs.
Would you mind hanging
with him for a bit?
- Well, where are you going?
- Something I gotta take care of.
Okay?
- But...
- [door opens]
[door closes]
[knock on door]
[door opens]
Ethan?
You doing okay?
- I'm fine.
- 'Cause I thought,
maybe you might wanna go
see something really cool.
My wife had visions
of this place.
Yeah, I've heard.
I thought she was crazy.
I should've listened to her.
Well... shoulda,
woulda, coulda, right?
What exactly makes you think
you're gonna be the
one to figure this out?
I imagine a lot of pretty
smart people have tried.
- [door opens]
- I'm smarter.
- Oh.
- Oh, please, come on in.
Make yourself at home.
It's done.
Right now.
Do you understand me?
What are we talking about?
Who the fuck do you think you
are dragging my wife and kid
out into the middle
of the woods?
Okay, first of all,
I didn't drag anybody anywhere...
- I only wanna say this once.
Tabitha is not in a
good place right now.
She doesn't need you
filling her head with ideas
about how somehow, she's
this chosen savior,
responsible for getting
everybody home...
You get your fucking
hands off me!
Filling her head with
ideas? What is she, nine?
Jim, she... she came
here! She came here, okay?
She saw the drawings, she
recognized the, uh, s...
You know what? I don't need
to explain this to you.
All right, then, let
me explain this to you.
You are a lonely, selfish,
narcissistic asshole,
who doesn't give a shit
about anything but yourself
and your own goddamn ego.
If you wanna kill yourself
trying to figure this thing out,
be my guest.
But I have a family
to look out for.
- Mm.
- I have people
who mean more to me than
you will ever understand.
Jim, I'm getting a little tired
of this sanctimonious
blue-collar bullshit.
You wanna talk
about your family?
Let's talk about your
family. Of the two of us,
I am the only one doing a
goddamn thing to help them!
[scoffs]
Look at this! You see this?
This... this helps people!
No! You know what this does?!
This shows people how
you are the smartest
fucking prick in the room!
So what?!
If it gets us home,
who gives a shit?!
And I'm not gonna do this.
I'm sorry. I'm
not gonna do this.
I'm not gonna waste
any more of my time.
Listen, if you wanna keep
your kids under lock and key,
more power to you.
Tabitha's a grown-up.
You got a problem with what
she's doing, talk to her.
Sorry. We're not done here!
Yeah, we fucking are, Jim!
[grunts]
Well, that was
certainly productive.
[Ellis] Fatima?
Hey. Come here.
We're gonna get this
through this, okay?
Ellis, I need you and your
dad to stop saying that.
I killed someone.
How, I mean... help me.
No, listen to
me. Listen to me.
Whatever this is,
it's you and I.
We are in this together.
I don't care if we need
to take that talisman
and go live in the woods.
No. You don't understand.
Ellis, whatever is inside me,
whatever made me...
it's still there.
- No. Babe, hey.
- It's still there. I...
What if it happens again?
What if I... what if I...
what if I do something...
You... You won't. You won't.
Look at me. Look at me.
You won't. Okay?
Because you are
stronger than this.
Whatever this is, we
are stronger than this.
Okay?
Fatima?
Okay.
I brought you some things.
Some...
Some clothes if
you wanna change.
- [bag thuds]
- Hey...
Lucky handkerchief. Remember?
I love you.
I love you, too.
Okay.
I'll be back soon.
Okay. Soon.
[shrieking and gasping]
[ominous music playing]
[sighs]
♪♪♪
[breathing shakily]
[inhaling sharply]
♪♪♪
[camera shutter clicks]
You mind if I give you
some unsolicited advice?
I don't see why not.
Maybe, sometimes, when
you're with your wife...
you should shut the
fuck up and listen.
Excuse me?
Jim, I-I look at you right now.
All I see is me standing
there 40 years ago.
I was so sure I could "fix" her.
[chuckles] It never occurred
to me she wasn't broken.
That, uh... arrogant fella
who stormed outta here?
He... He was right
about one thing.
What you're doing,
how tight you're holding
on to everything...
You may tell yourself you're
doing it for your family.
But you're doing it
because you're scared,
and you're doing
it for yourself.
I'm probably the only
guy in this whole place
who can tell you that
and say... it's true.
It's true.
[glass clatters]
Uh, you want a drink?
No. I don't...
- Oh.
- My dad was a drunk.
Mine, too.
The night my daughter was born,
after Tabitha fell asleep, I...
I went to the bar across the
street from the hospital,
and I asked the bartender
for the tallest glass
of whiskey she could pour,
and I stared at that
drink for hours,
and I promised myself I would
be a better father to my kids...
a better husband to my wife.
What are you doing?
Giving you the chance
to renew your vows.
Sit there as long as you like.
I could use the company.
What is this?
I don't know.
But if I tell you something,
can you promise that you
won't tell Mom and Dad?
Ever since I woke up,
something has been
happening in me.
I... I hear things in my head.
What kind of things?
I hear people screaming.
And it won't stop.
But yesterday,
I was out here with Randall,
and when I saw this place...
everything went quiet
for the first time
since I woke up.
But that's... good, right?
I don't know.
[inhales and exhales
deeply] I feel...
I feel like something...
Like it wants me to go in here.
And I don't know what to do.
It's just a pile
of rocks, right?
But I'm scared.
So... what do I do?
What?
All I keep thinking about
is that this sounds like
those stories that
you always tell us.
If I was a character in
one of those stories...
what would I do?
What would...
What would this be?
You're at a threshold.
It's always scary, but...
the hero has to be brave.
We can go in
together, if you want.
[crows cawing in distance]
Yeah.
Ready?
[ominous music playing]
♪♪♪
[gasping]
[breathing rapidly]
[whimpering]
[shrieking and
screaming in distance]
[screaming continues]
[screaming]
[gasps]
[screaming continues]
No! No! No!
[screaming]
Julie! Julie!
[grunting]
Help!
[Tabitha] Victor, do you
remember where you were
when you heard Jasper talk?
It was dark in a basement.
Do you remember which basement?
No, I don't... No,
I don't remember.
- Victor, it's fine.
- Yeah.
What were you doing
in the basement?
I don't remember!
I don't remember.
- Hey, don't do...
- Was it nice that day?
What?
The day you heard Jasper talk...
what was it like outside?
It was sunny. It
was... I was...
We were playing.
- Wait. You mean, you and Eloise?
- [Victor] Yeah.
Yeah. I was... We were
playing hide-and-seek.
- Yeah?
- 'Cause Eloise was good
at hide-and-seek.
I could never find her, no
matter how hard I looked.
Okay. Um...
Where did you look
that day, Victor?
Everywhere. The bar, the diner,
the houses, the... church.
I looked in the church.
She'd never hid there before.
- Mm-hmm?
- She said it always scared her,
but I'd already looked
everywhere else.
That was where it happened.
That's where I saw Jasper
talking to Christopher
in the church!
We just need to know
if you saw anything.
I mean, did I see
someone stab the old lady
in the greenhouse? No.
What about Tillie? When was
the last time you saw her?
I don't know.
Yesterday morning.
Why aren't you guys talking
to the one person in town
who actually murdered someone?
What?
Oh, you don't know about Sara?
She doesn't know about Sara.
Look, I'm not sure why you
guys are talking to us.
It's pretty fuckin'
obvious who did this.
Okay, look, we're gonna
talk to Sara after.
- But for right now, let's...
- Didn't she kill your Dad?
The fuck are you
defending her for?
Goddamnit, I said no!
Then what is your solution?!
Okay, we are running
out of time, okay?!
Maybe... maybe if
you explain to them,
all right, and then give
it a little bit of time...
And in the meantime,
what? What?
You two are living
out there in a tent?
Yes! We'll have
talismans! We'll be safe!
You won't be safe from her.
So, that... is that
what you're afraid of?
- Whatever made her do this...
- She would never hurt me.
She just stabbed someone
in the fucking chest!
Son, listen to me!
I love Fatima. I do. But
we do not know what...
Boyd, look, I have a whole
lot of people up there
just ready to march on
Sara's house with torches...
What's going on?
It wasn't Sara.
Boyd, look, I know
you care about her...
It was Fatima.
[Donna stammers]
Was what that guy said about
Sara and your dad true?
[sighs] It's not that simple.
Okay, you didn't think it
was worth mentioning the girl
that already
murdered two people?
Look, it's just, uh,
she's different now,
and Boyd trusts her.
Who gives a shit what
Boyd thinks, okay?
- [Ethan] Help!
- You know, you people got
a real funny way...
- I need help!
Hey, hey. What's
wrong? What's wrong?
Julie! She's on the
ground! She's shaking!
- Okay. Wait, wait, wait.
- Come on, we have to help her!
[screaming]
Tell it to stop!
[voices shrieking]
[shrieking and screaming stop]
[breathing rapidly]
[Martin] You have to climb!
[Boyd] What? No. I ca...
[Boyd groans]
I can't!
[Martin] Wait.
Julie?
- How do you know my name?
- He needs the rope.
Please.
[breathing rapidly]
Who is that?
[Boyd] Hey, what... Fuck!
What?
[Martin] You have to hurry!
They'll be back soon.
Okay.
[Julie breathing rapidly]
Thank you.
- Who's down there?
- [Martin] You need to leave.
It isn't safe here.
Go!
[rustling]
[breathing rapidly] What...
[whimpering] Plea...
[Tabitha] No, no, Victor.
Can you just please tell me
what's going on? Where are we?
[Victor, whispering]
We're underneath the town.
This is where the monsters live.
This is where they sleep,
but I can get us out.
[Tabitha] They what?
Mom?
[child] Anghkooey!
[child 2] Anghkooey!
[children] Anghkooey!
Anghkooey! Anghkooey!
Please...
[voices screaming]
[Ethan] Julie! Julie! Julie!
- Just get her up. Julie!
- [Acosta] Come here.
- I got you.
- [Kenny] Just get her up.
[screaming]
- [Kenny] Hey, hey, hey, hey!
- [Ethan] Julie!
- Hey. Hey.
- It's okay. It's okay.
Oh, my God.
What happened?
- Are you okay?
So I took her outta town
before everyone woke up.
You need to bring her back.
I can't do that. Not yet.
- Not until we...
- Until you what?
Manage to resurrect Tillie?
Look, I don't wanna...
I love Fatima as
though she were my own.
But we have a town we have
to worry about here, Boyd.
And if you try to hide
this, and people find out...
They will understand, just
like they did with Sara.
Is that what you
think? You think they
understood about Sara?
- Yes.
No, no, no! They
didn't understand.
They accepted it.
People swallowed it.
But they certainly
did not understand it!
They let it go because
you told them they had to.
Great, then, I will
tell them again!
- It's not gonna work this time.
- Why not?
Because they don't
believe in you anymore.
Not like they did.
I'll tell them I did it.
- No, no, no!
- No, no, I'll, I'll... I did it!
- No, no, no, it's not enough!
- Why?
Because it doesn't change
that it made it happen
in the first place!
There is either something
horrible growing inside of her,
or else this place has
finally broken her mind!
Either way, it's only a matter
of time before it happens again!
They can stay with me.
[exhales heavily]
She won't be a threat
to anyone else.
I can watch her.
We can watch her.
No, no, no, Boyd. Boyd, you
may both want this to be okay,
and God knows I want
it to be okay, too.
But if you are not gonna
tell everyone, then I am.
Please, don't make me do this.
[door closes]
What are you doing?
You're gonna need supplies.
[Victor] It was in the basement.
It happened in the basement.
When I opened the
door, I heard voices.
So, I was quiet, and I
wanted to get closer.
When I got...
to the bottom of the stairs,
Jasper was telling secrets.
[muted speech]
- [muted speech]
- Christopher got angry.
[continues, muted]
No, no, that's not right.
It wasn't Jasper.
[muted speech continues]
It was the boy in white.
He was the one
that was down here.
He who was telling
secrets to Christopher.
[muted] The answers to the
end are at the beginning.
He said, "The answers to the
end are at the beginning."
[boy in white, muted] It
started with the children.
That it started
with the children...
- What the others did to them.
What others, Victor?
The people they loved.
The people they trusted.
The children are
born in the dark.
[Victor] He said the children
were born in the dark.
[boy in white, muted] And then
they were murdered in the dark.
And then they were
murdered... in the dark.
[muted] But someone
who loved them...
But someone who loved them...
- told them a story.
- Told them a story.
The story gave them hope.
And when the children
laid on the stones,
they poured their hope
into the roots that
made the symbol,
and those roots became the tree.
The Faraway Tree.
The boy in white was
trying to tell Christopher
that to save the children...
he would have to go
through the tree.
But he wouldn't... he
wouldn't listen, and he...
he got angry.
[muted] You're a liar!
Everything lies here!
Christopher wouldn't
listen, so I-I...
What?
Christopher wouldn't
go to the tree, so...
I told my mother what
the boy in white said.
And that's why she left us.
[Elgin] Fatima?
It's Elgin.
[door creaks open]
You...
Okay, stay close, all
right? But not too close.
Four or five hours out,
that should be, uh, enough.
[Ellis] Okay.
And, whatever you do, you stay
off the path to the settlement.
Last thing we want is anybody
tripping over your tent.
I'm gonna leave supplies for
you at the shack twice a week.
You need anything, you
leave a note behind.
- Okay.
- You bring a pen and pad?
Yeah, it's in the pack.
And if things...
Look, if things get worse,
you promise me that you'll...
Look, um, Dad,
I know you don't
want me to do this,
but if you'd had the chance,
if you and Mom coulda ran,
even after she did
what she did...
what would you have done?
[whispers] Come on.
Let's go. Come on. Come on.
No.
Fatima?!
What? Fatima!
Fatima!
- Almost there.
- Elgin, where are we going?
It's just through
here. It's...
Are you sure we're supposed
to be this close to town?
I told you.
Ellis is waiting for you.
Right here,
there's a room down here
that nobody knows about.
[grunts]
Come on. Please.
Fatima.
[breathing heavily]
It's right through there.
[Fatima] Ellis?
I, uh, I'll wait for
him at the shack.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
You can't do that.
Elgin, get out of my way.
No, you don't understand.
You have to be here.
It's the only place that
the baby will be safe.
- There is no baby.
- Yes, there is.
It... It's just not yours.
Elgin, get out of my way.
Get out of my way!
Get out of my...
Elgin! Get out of my way!
- Fatima!
- Aah! [groans]
[groans]
[gasping and groaning]
You see?
The baby knows you have to stay.
[groaning] Elgin, stop.
Fighting it is just
going to make it worse.
Elgin, get out of my way.
Please, get out of my way.
Get out of my way!
[panting]
I'm sorry.
[gasping]
I really am.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
No! No!
This is for the best.
No, please! Help!
Help!
Elgin, no!
Elgin, please!
Help! Aah!
Help! Help!
Help!
♪♪♪